work-at-home-forum.com 2017-02-03

# Privacy Policy for Work at Home Forum | Work at Home Forum

Work at Home Forum privacy policy.

Work at Home Forum has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to privacy of our users.  
The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Work at Home Forum (http://www.work-at-home-forum.com).   

## Registration

Although users can freely read the forum topics and posts, we require users to create an account to post or reply by selecting an username and providing their email address.   

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Personally Identifiable Information

Other than the email address, which the user can opt to disclose to other members, any information provided at the time of registration or through modification of user profile is disclosed in the member's profile page and is viewable by other members.   

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.   

### Logging and Administration

We use your IP address for administration of this website. To log members, we use cookies.   

### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. Work at Home Forum is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.   

### Newsletters

We may send special offers and related news once a week to those who have opted for at the time of registration or through any optin form on the website. Users may chose to unsubscribe at any given time using the unsubscribe link in each mailing. We do not share or trade the email addresses of users with any third party.   

### Advertisements

We use third-party advertising companies, like Google, to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).   

### Public Forums

The information posted in the forums is made available to general public and hence due caution should be exercised while sharing personal information.   

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement and/or the practices of this site, you can contact:  
Work at Home Forum  
Flat no. 1002, Abhiman Gardens  
Near City Hospital, Kadri  
Mangalore - 575003  
Karnataka, India  
Email: admin at work-at-home-forum.com
